<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Zen Technologies</title>
    <link>zentech.services/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Zen Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="zentech.services/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development</title>
      <link>zentech.services/services/software-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>zentech.services/services/software-development/</guid>
      <description>Zen Technologies has a proven track record of providing custom application development and maintenance services to its clients in various industries, with an ability to handle large enterprise systems and provide cost effective and on time support.
We provide end-to-end software development solutions – right from conception to production promotion. We strictly follow Agile methodology, this helps us meet our clients requirements by delivering SOLID product within expected time and budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Re-Engineering</title>
      <link>zentech.services/services/software-reengingeering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>zentech.services/services/software-reengingeering/</guid>
      <description>Our application migration and re-engineering services help our clients transit their mission critical application from legacy platforms to current, state-of-the art technologies, using our proven methodology, best practices and tools. We add value by providing contemporary, web- based graphical user interface for modernizing legacy with our in-depth knowledge of emerging technologies and third party tools.
Migration Services By migrating your legacy products from older legacy technologies, to new state-of-the-art platforms, your custom software products will benefit from improved integration capabilities, faster acceptance in the market and increased scalability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managed Services</title>
      <link>zentech.services/services/managed-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>zentech.services/services/managed-services/</guid>
      <description>In today’s competitive business climate, companies are looking for capabilities and services that can enable them to perform more efficiently. At Zen Technologies, we offer our expert managed IT services that are targeted at equipping your company with dynamic and professional solutions for managing and organizing your IT environment.
Planning Zen Technologies has a custom process to analyse key points in your technology setup and develop a road map within your budget to evolve your technology, quarter after quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resource Consulting</title>
      <link>zentech.services/services/resource-consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>zentech.services/services/resource-consulting/</guid>
      <description>Zen’s primary objective is to provide exceptional service and value for time and efforts.
Project Consulting The important challenge of project and delivery management is to ensure that a project is delivered within defined constraints.
Our approach to the delivery of our client’s project is simple. Zen identifies appropriate practice and techniques for managing projects on your behalf. Our team work closely with you to ensure that your organization achieve the best results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Maintenance</title>
      <link>zentech.services/services/software-maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>zentech.services/services/software-maintenance/</guid>
      <description>In current scenario, business practices, policies and methodologies undergoes continuous changes to adopt to newer, better and emerging technologies. This keeps every on toes to manage their IT requirements at the same time capitalizing on current assets.
Software maintenance and enhancement is one of the most important phase of the development life cycle. Maintenance process represents the enhancements and improvements to existing system which keeps the system scalable. Zen Technologies helps organization to achieve this task with an industry proven approaches and patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMS Development</title>
      <link>zentech.services/services/cms-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>zentech.services/services/cms-management/</guid>
      <description>We provide niche and affordable CMS (content management solutions) that delivers higher level of functionality compared to traditional static websites. Our expertise in various opensource CMS systems like WordPress, Magento and Joomla allows us to serve our customers with highly scalable and self-manageable websites. Our user-friendly and easy to use CMS empowers any organization to become comfortable with website management and make the site dynamic.
Integrated Website Analytics Track the life cycle of your Website visitors via CMS integration with analytic tools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>